{
    "id": "95d94843dc1a4f6da7172592a819fd52",
    "title": "Prepositions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "He has been ill …………………… three months.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d45e6430da6e47ea8cbee788c169e63c"
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t played football ………………….. a long time.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "since",
                "from"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "a3e4937a76c245e8a27543bff023c9bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "This cloth is inferior …………………. that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "than",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "37d47f98d6b849be85b3b8de736701ab"
        },
        {
            "question": "Everybody should pray ………………….. God.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "for",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a772bac5275940159cdd38c29bfb840d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He wrote ………………….. me.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "at",
                "to",
                "with"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f4e6b0d5b27b476a87a62dde5dd59139"
        },
        {
            "question": "Can you explain this ………………… me?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "for",
                "with",
                "to"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "06109ece43bd41bc854df3ab97523984"
        },
        {
            "question": "Are you still ………………….. the same address?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "on",
                "in",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "89a12ea0481a4868865bf0f2b6522edf"
        },
        {
            "question": "Send this letter …………………… my new address.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cb93ba2b5bc747d986c82100cc8fd1e2"
        },
        {
            "question": "He goes …………………. school.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "to",
                "for",
                "at"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0b4bfd6069f44451b667c8554833d091"
        },
        {
            "question": "I am obliged ………………….. you for this good turn.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "with",
                "to",
                "for"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "2805cc90a76443a5995a5aedcb4c3b63"
        }
    ]
}